Beleza, não faça essas quatro coisas no 4º de setembro de 2025. Você não dirá que não eu não lhe escutei mais, certo?
Isso será um dos mais poderosos e dangerousos dias do ano 2025! Um portal de energia estará aberto.
E se você faz uma feita, sua vida, em adição a não prosperar, pode ir voltando.
O dinheiro pode ir derrotando você. E você pode desbloquear o seu fio personal por um longo tempo.
Mas se você sabe o que fazer e eu te ensino...
Se você vibra em the right way and I will help you, you can unblock the channel of confidence of wealth and manifest a new reality with security, abundance, balance and stability.
And the best part is, I will show you exactly how you will do it.
In this video, I will tell you the 4 things you cannot do under any circumstances.
On the day of April 4th and the 4 things you need to do to cross this portal with awareness and activate a new frequency of confidence of wealth and prosperity in your life.
So do the following, fulfill our agreement.
If you're here, leave a like. If you're just arriving, if you want to know more about the portal, but don't want to like it yet, I challenge you.
Give it a dislike, and at the end of the video you can change it to a like. I'm doing this challenge because I'm aware of the power of the content I'm going to bring you today.
And look, a special message for those who participated in the secrets of NLP in practice.
You're going to receive my new book as a gift, completely free of charge and with your name printed on the first historical and collectors edition.
Insist, persist and never give up, the power to co-create the life you deserve. The link is in the description of this video here, pinned in the comments.
If you don't know if you're entitled to receive the book as a gift, click on the link and then you'll find out. Imagine that.
Thousands of people, millions of people will buy this book. They'll have this book in their homes and your name will be printed on a special thank you section.
Imagine the vibration of that, a vibration in history, the transformation in the lives of all these people, and your name is not a segregor.
This will bring a lot of positive energy into your life, it's the beginning of a new cycle, there's just one detail.
It can only be requested until April 6th. The link is in the description of the video, pinned in the comments.
So, click on this link right away to add your name to the book.
If you watch this video after April 6th, there's a gift for you too. You'll be able to get the new manifestation code.
The link is in the description. Click here, find out if you're entitled to the book and which book is available for you.
Now you're going to stay with me until the end, because this video is the 444 sign you've been waiting for.
I'm going to teach you how to cross the portal with the right vibration.
So, do the following, take a deep breath and get ready because now you're crossing of the 44 energy portal of confidence and wealth begins.
If you're watching this video between April 4th, 2025 and April 12th, 2025, the 444 sign has arrived in your life.
Do you know what that means? I'll explain. So, write it down here. I accept and receive the 444 signal. Do you know what the 444 signal is?
Do you know why April 4th is so important? Let me explain. The 444 is one of the most powerful signals in the universe.
We in the universe form a unique system. Let me explain something to you here. How does the law of attraction work?
The law of attraction acts in a reality, in a dimension that mirrors ours, called the universal flow field.
Tell me in the comments if you've heard about it. In the law of attraction, many people call it the universe.
It's a nickname that people give to this flow field. It's not the right name, it's not the universe, it's an energy field.
Making an analogy for you to understand. It's like the Internet. The Internet is not in the cloud.
This energy field is more or less like that. And it is a mirror of our reality.
Nothing happens on the physical plane that doesn't happen on the energetic plane. Everything you think, you feel, you vibrate.
This energy goes to the flow field and organizes itself and, through the law of attraction, returns to the physical plane.
Since we form a single system, these two realities connect and the universe sends us many signals.
One of these powerful signals is 444. When this number, this numerical sequence, starts to appear in your life, it represents trust.
The universe is trying to tell you, look, what you asked for will come. Your wishes will be granted, money will come, wealth will come. Do you accept it? Quote, that's what the universe is giving you, because if you're watching this video, it's not by chance.
You're receiving the 444 signal. So, right here, I accept and receive the 444 signal.
It will bring absolute trust, firm faith, emotional stability, balance, concrete fulfillment of your dreams and activation of wealth.
It's as if the universal flow field is telling you, you're on the right path.
Trust. What you manifested is on its way for you to receive. Quote.
In the study of numbers, in vibrational biology, the number 4 carries the energy of structure, of the solid foundation of prosperity and is sustained over time.
Now imagine this vibration tripled in the 444 signal. And that is what we are going to take advantage of on the emblematic date of the 44 portal.
The following is the case. April 4 is considered a rare and powerful energy portal.
It aligns your personal flow field with this universal flow field.
Your router, your heart, the router of your soul, of your energy field, connects more strongly on April 4 with the universal flow field.
And everything that you emanate as a signal on that day, in the days before that day and in the days right after, they intensify in the universal flow field.
It is an open channel of manifestation. Everything that you are emanating here will arrive 4 times faster. And there is something that no one tells you.
This 444 signal is not something that you only receive. You can also emit it. You must have heard about the signs of the universe.
There is a lot of content about this on the internet. But what no one tells you is that, since it is a two-way street, a personal flow field and a universal flow field, I don't just need to receive it.
You are receiving the 444 signal, but on April 4 we are going to intensify it. We are going to emit this 444 signal, telling the universe,
"Hey, look here, I am ready to receive my dreams, my desires, lots of money, lots of wealth, lots of joy, lots of happiness, lots of health."
And when the universe sends you the 444, it is telling you, "You can trust, your dreams will come, the money will come." And when you write, feel it vibrate, the 444 in the right way, you say to the universe, "I'm ready, you can send it."
It's the perfect union, the perfect date, you're going to miss this opportunity. Something magical happens on this date.
When you do this, your individual field enters into resonance with the universal field, in this unique system, and you co-create reality at an alarming speed.
And that's why on April 4, 2025, on the day of the portal, I'll be live with you.
We'll have a frequency field where intention, emotion, vibration meet and multiply.
And if you're here watching this video, it's not a coincidence. There's no coincidence in the universe. Everything is in the right place, at the right time. And this video is a call for you. It's the 444 signal in your life.
That's why I want you to write here in the comments. I accept and I receive the 444 signal. It will confirm that the universe is ready to deliver you.
And remember, look, if you're watching this video before April 4, I'll all be live on April 4 at 7pm right here on YouTube.
So subscribe to the channel and activate the bell so you can receive notifications. I'm going to do a very powerful activation. I'm a professor of Neurolinguistic Programming, so I combine NLP, Neurolinguistic Programming with the law of attraction.
We can get into the exact vibrational state that we need.
Imagine the following, it's like the dow of a radio. Are you from that time? Tell me here in the comments if you're from that time.
In the past, for younger people, radios weren't like they are today, where you could just put on a station and listen. You had to pick it up and keep turning it like this.
Look, turn a little wheel and tune in to a specific station on your dial. The universe is the same thing. So, what am I going to do?
On April 4, I'm going to conduct a powerful technique in which we're going to tune your mind to the frequency of the things you want.
And it's going to be wonderful. You're going to feel that what you want is coming.
You will feel such immense faith in your heart. I will be live at 7pm, and hey, there's one detail. I'll send all the information to my WhatsApp group. Tell me in the comments if you're already in the group.
If you're not in the group, you'll click the link in the video description here or pinned in the comments.
You'll receive the book as a gift, insist, persist, and never give up. After you've completed the process to receive your book, I'll send you the link to the group, then you join the group and receive the invitation to all the live sessions.
On April 4, powerful activation and portal crossing. And then I'll be live on Sunday 2, on the 6th, at 10.30am, so we can complete the great portal crossing in a super activation. Why?
We need to keep this frequency up there, at the frequency of your desires, from the 4th to the 12th. Look, there's one more thing. You'll receive the book as a gift and it will have your name printed on it.
You already have a book at home, an important, historical, collector's book with your name on it. It will be printed, and the thank you section with your name on it will come out of the printer, but that is only possible until the 6th.
So, if you are watching this video after the 6th, you will no longer be able to receive this book, but the link is here, looked, and you can win this one after the 6th, okay?
So, if you haven't filled out this form yet, the link is in the video description or pinned in the comments.
Now that you understand the 444 signal, you understand what the 44 portal is and why it speeds up everything in your life, pay close attention, because there are 4 things, 4 attitudes that you absolutely cannot do on April 4.
And if you do these 4 things, you completely block your manifestation, you block the flow of abundance and you may attract more scarcity and more pain into your life.
Number one, don't complain.
Don't complain, what is complaining? Complaining is asking. Get that into your head.
On April 4 and in the period before and after April 4, words have a multiplied power.
When you complain, you send a clear message to the universe, and you know what you're saying. I want more of this.
If you complain about not having money, you're saying, hey, I want more lack of money. If you complain about your illness, you say, hey, I want more illness.
If you complain about your problems, you're asking for more problems.
Everything you complain about on April 4 will come back 4 times stronger into your life.
So, silence your complaints, exchange complaints for intentions, focus on what you want and not on what's bothering you.
Number two, don't talk to people or yourself about the things you no longer want in your life.
It's simple. The universe doesn't understand and know.
When you say, I don't want any more pain. The universe says, your wish is my command. Take it, I don't want to suffer anymore.
The universe says, your wish is my command. Take the suffering.
At Portal 44, the universe's response is faster. So, what are you going to do? Talk only about what you want.
Change what you don't want. Find out what you want instead and talk about it.
I don't want to live like this anymore. Change that for I accept from now on to live with joy, abundance and freedom.
And number three, don't think about past pains anymore.
This is a silent mistake that blocks everything in your life.
You thought about hurts, remembered betrayals, felt angry again, connected to the frequency of a trauma, and that's it, blocked vibration.
At Portal 44, you emanate this to the universe. This energy comes back with more negative things for your life.
In a vicious cycle of repetition, you manifest more of what you felt, even if it happened many years ago.
And then I'm going to teach you something.
If you have memories from your past that bother you and that lower your vibration, go here on my channel, in the most recent videos on my channel, where you will find a neuro-linguistic programming technique.
And in this technique we will turn off the emotion of pain and suffering from anything that has happened in your life.
It is possible, and I will prove it to you. Do you know how, I will ask you here, look.
Whoever is watching this video and has already erased pain, a painful memory from the past, leave your story here so you can show the people who are watching this video that it is possible and so they can go to the next video and erase that memory.
And you who are going to leave here, go there and erase a painful memory, then you come back here and say, "Look, I went there and it worked. Let's make this a chain of goodness."
Because after all, this is a powerful moment for you to free yourself, to accept living with joy, abundance and freedom.
You don't need to suffer twice. No one needs to suffer more than once. Once, okay? So go there, do the technique and then come back here and tell me.
And number four, don't judge others.
Everything you judge about others, you send to the universe. Connect to the frequency and receive negative things in your life.
Judgment contaminates your vibration.
Quando you judge, you automatically divert the focus of your creative energy.
And the universe understands that you are vibrating in scarcity, comparison, separation.
Judgment has an extremely low vibration in the portal.
Your focus should be on yourself, on your evolution, on your frequency.
These are the four behaviors that you cannot have on April 4.
So, write this down.
April 4 is a bridge to a new reality and you need to cross it with your vibration clean, lined, and conscious.
Do you promise me that you will avoid these four things? That you will avoid making these four mistakes?
Tell me your comments here and I will give you a tip. There is a gravavoid code, it is like this. Look, 71,931. It helps you block any energy.
I am a professor of Neurolinguistic programming, so, if you feel that you connected over the next few days, not just on four quarters, in any of these four things that lowered your vibration, at that moment you adjust your posture and say, 71,931 cancels.
71,931 cancels. 71,931 cancels.
At this point, there's a little bit of science, okay? A little bit of neuroscience here. When you do this, you will close a neural network that opened from a low vibration emotional state and then you will choose a positive thought. Focus on gratitude. Focus on gratitude and you will change any negative feeling.
Now there's an important detail. I want to remind you of the book, okay? Look, it's only until the 6th. If you haven't gotten it yet, click the link in the description here and pin it in the comments. You will receive it with your name printed on the first historic collector's edition.
And remember that on four quarters I will be live starting at 7pm and on Sunday, the 6th, I will be live starting at 10.30am with activation at 11.11am.
If you've come this far, it's because you felt this calling.
This calling is for you. You received the 444 signal and you're not in this video by chance. You've already liked it. You've already written here. I accept. I receive the 444 signal. Go get your book as a gift.
So, pay attention now, because I'm going to give you 4 sacred actions that you can not only do, but I recommend that you do as homework on April 4th so that you can reach this frequency of confidence, of wealth.
If you start doing them from today, I don't know what day you're watching this video, leave them in the comments here and do them by the 12th. These 4 things that I'm going to tell you, your life will change over the next few days, the next few months, the next few years.
If you're watching this video before April 4th, before 7pm, do these 4 things, because when you get to the live with me at 7pm, you'll be at the ideal frequency.
We're going to activate this frequency. We're going to scale it to the maximum and we're going to raise your frequency to a level you've never imagined.
1. Practice gratitude. Intentional gratitude.
Live in a state of grace, of gratitude. Be very thankful. Be thankful for everything you already have.
Now, especially, be thankful for what you don't have yet. Be thankful for the healing that has already manifested. Be thankful for the money that is already arriving.
Gratitude is the vibrational key that opens the portal for you to cross.
It's what signals to the universe. Hey, hey, I trust, I receive, I accept.
Feel gratitude in your heart. Write it down, speak it out loud, keep a gratitude journal, a gratitude jar, write things down, put them in the jar.
During this period, you won't ask for anything, you'll just be thankful, thankful as if you had already received it.
2. Keep your vibration high.
Your vibration is the magnet and everything will come back to you faster. If you keep your vibration high, you will receive four times more.
And yes, throughout the day, the days before and after the portal day, you will do this with more strength, with more intensity.
But something will always come up to throw you off balance. Maybe someone, a piece of news, a memory.
And here you will have a secret weapon, the NLP state breaking technique, which I mentioned earlier, 71931 cancel.
If anything lowers your vibration, you say 71931 cancel, 71931 cancel, 71931 cancel. Close that thought.
Lift your head, choose the new thought of gratitude. Come back to gratitude. Come back to gratitude. Focus on it.
3. Share your light.
4/4 portal is about receiving, but it is also about transmitting.
That is why throughout the day, 4/04, in the days before and the days after, talk to people about God, talk about Jesus, about what you believe in your soul.
Share with someone a verse that strengthens you.
Talk about the portal, about good things, about energy. Spread faith, spread hope, intention. Give attention to those who need it.
Remember, those who share, expand.
The more you expand this energy, the more it comes back multiplied.
One way to do this is to share this video with people.
So, press share and send this powerful energy from the portal.
4. Be live with me during the activation of the portal.
It's a call.
On April 4, 7pm, Brasilia time. I will be live on YouTube leading the crossing of the portal.
Thousands of people from all over the world who will choose to live a new cycle with you.
And together we will do a deep vibrational activation. We will reach a vibration that you have never experienced in your life. If you have never done this, you don't know what you are missing.
Powerful, convinced faith to seal a new phase.
And this moment will go down in your history. And on Sunday I will also be live at 10.30am with activation at 11.11am so, one detail.
If you're not in the group yet, don't waste any time. Click the link in the video description here or in the comments.
You'll receive the book insist, persist and never give up, the power to co-create the life you deserve.
Your name will be printed in the first historic collector's edition.
After you complete the process to receive the book, you'll receive the link to join the exclusive group and participate with us.
You'll participate in the wealth challenge and the money trail.
The link is in the video description pinned in the comments.
The fourth is a day that will mark your life. You'll remember the fourth of April 2025 for the rest of your journey.
Remember, you didn't get here by chance. This is a calling. It's the 444 signal arriving in your life.
The 4 to 4 portal is a unique moment and you received the calling with an extraordinary vibrational force that will open the paths, unlock your abundance and accelerate your deepest desires.
So, remember to be live with me on 4.04, 7pm after a Sunday at 10.30am on the 6th, activation at 11.11am.
And also remember to get your book here in the description of this video and pin it in the comments.
Final message.
If you have any painful memories from the past, any pain, something that bothers you, take a look at my channel, which has a tool to erase this pain.
If you are afraid of something, panicked about something, there is a tool for that too.
Explore the channel, then subscribe, like it, activate the reminder, you will enjoy it a lot.
And I want to invite you. Let's go together.
You are welcome to join me on an incredible journey of transformation, a bare version of ourselves.
M.